wedoist.com 2014-02-09

# Wedoist Privacy Policy

**

Your privacy is critically important to us.

At Wedoist we have a few fundamental principles:

**

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.
  * Although Wedoist owns the code, databases, and all rights to the Wedoist application, you retain all rights to your data.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals: 

### Your data

Wedoist uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run Wedoist. Although Wedoist owns the code, databases, and all rights to the Wedoist application, you retain all rights to the data you add to Wedoist. 

### Ads

We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Wedoist collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Wedoist’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Wedoist’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Wedoist may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. 

Wedoist also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Wedoist does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below. 

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Wedoist’s websites choose to interact with Wedoist in ways that require Wedoist to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Wedoist gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a blog at Wedoist.com to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Wedoist are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Wedoist collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Wedoist. Wedoist does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. 

### Aggregated Statistics

Wedoist may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Wedoist may monitor how many tasks gets completed each day. Wedoist may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Wedoist does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. 

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Wedoist discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Wedoist’s behalf or to provide services available at Wedoist’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Wedoist’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Wedoist will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Wedoist discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Wedoist believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Wedoist, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Wedoist website and have supplied your email address, Wedoist may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Wedoist and our products. We expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Wedoist takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

We use cookies to store visitors preferences, customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends. Cookies are required to use Wedoist.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Wedoist may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Wedoist’s sole discretion. Wedoist encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change. 

### Copyright

Wedoist privacy policy is released under [Creative Commons Sharealike](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/2.5/) license.
